

PATRYK CISZEWSKI

Site Reliability Engineer | DevOps | Administrator 🗣 SALFORD, M50 2EQ, UNITED KINGDOM | +44 07908720156

O DETAILS O

MediaCityUK, Blue, Salford, M50 2EQ, United Kingdom +44 07908720156 elkonadsgn@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

04-10-1995 Kozienice

NATIONALITY

Polish

DRIVING LICENSE

In progress

o SKILLS o

Monitoring - Zabbix | Nagios | CloudWatch

IaaC (Puppet hiera/terraform)

CI/CD automation (Jenkins/Ansible)

Cloud Computing (GCP/AWS)

Atlassian stack (Jira + Confluence)

Logging stacks (Elasticsearch|Splunk|SumoLogic))

> WebServers (Apache, Nginx, Tomcat)

Virtualization (KVMS|Vmware|Vsphere|Dells)

Databases (Mysql|MongoDB|RDS)

Alerting (PagerDuty|StatusCake)

MailServers (POSTFIX)

Version control (Git|SVN)

Unix(Centos5&7 + RHEL7)

Scripting (Bash|Python)

Remote Administration

Remote Troubleshooting

IT operations

Grafana

O HOBBIES O

PROFILE

A system administrator with vast IT experience. Skills include computer networking, analytical thinking and creative problem-solving. I'm very open-minded, willing to work hard to progress and achieve my goals. Trying to be always, loyal, accurate and focused on duties. My mindset is focused on DevOps methodology of IoT and continuous delivery. I am passionate about Linux Sys administration and cloud technologies with a focus around uptime and monitoring of infrastructure.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Operations Engineer at BBC, Manchester

June 2019 — November 2019

Working in Digital 247/365 I am part of a team responsible for logging, investigating, fixing and escalating issues that occur on the BBC's wide range of digital platforms. This includes iPlayer both provided by the BBC and other parties who carry it on their services, websites that may be suffering from technical or content related issue and many of the tools used in the day to day activities of the wider BBC operations

Used Tech:

AWS (SQS, EC2, SES & CloudWatch), Linux, Tomcat java containers, Python (data extraction from APIs), Bash, Apache, IIS, Zenoss Enterprise Monitoring, Nagios, HP Operations Manager, JIRA, Confluence, Dynatrace synthetic monitoring, VMWare VSphere

Freelancer at Gurudesigns, Manchester

November 2018 — June 2019

Freelancing around various projects including working with:

- -Platforms on AWS, Network, Lamp stacks
- -AWS (EC2|RDS|CloudWatch|ELBS|LoadBalancing|R53)
- -GCP (Managing of resources)
- -Building Websites around (Wordpress, WebRTC Node+Sails.js)

Junior Site Reliability Engineer at EGNYTE, Poznan dept.

April 2018 — November 2018

I Was working for DevOps Department located in Poland for company from San Jose which is competition to Dropbox and Google Drive. It was Pure SaaS environment. My tasks include mainly maintenance of monitoring systems, as well as adding new features to it. Examples:

- -Working in ITIL Methodology
- -Writing RCA for support

Crossfit, Books, Devops culture, Hiking, Cooking, System administration, Military, Fitness, Video Production, Graphic Designs

○ LANGUAGES ○

English

Polish

o LINKS o

Linkedin

- -Managing incidents and statuspage updates
- -Administrating Linux Servers (2000+ servers) hardening, performance tuning
- -Writing terraform code/hiera configs
- -Maintenance tasks on site
- -Performing website pushes
- -Creating and adding new VM's to rotation
- -Running configuration updates
- -Running deployment jobs
- -Extending monitoring (migration of checks from Nagios to Zabbix)
- -Supporting automation of manual tasks
- -Working with kanban board
- -Managing operations team escalations
- -Reacting to all production/QA environments alerts/triggers/checks during business hours

System Administrator at ComRaid S.C, poznan (poland)

November 2017 — February 2018

I was working for an IT company which was outsourcing various services and administrations for public (schools) and medical sector as well as private companies.

Main tasks were focused around:

- -Preparation of workspaces and environments for workers
- -Hardware/Software repairs and troubleshooting
- -Network and security audits
- -CCTV Lan and Wireless
- -Networks | VPNs | CRM |
- -Building Workrooms from zero to end user experience

EDUCATION

Zespół Szkół Łączności im. Mikołaja Kopernika w Poznaniu, poznań

October 2012 — October 2015

- -Networking Routing | DNS | OSI\TCP | Services | Binary
- -Programming C++ | C# | Algorithms
- -Windows Troubleshooting | DOS troubleshooting
- -System Administration Service | Process management
- Build of Computer | Schemas | Architectures

Zespół Szkół Ekonomicznych im. Stanisława Staszica, Poznań

October 2015 — October 2016

COURSES

Advanced Suse Linux administration,

October 2018 — Present

Terraform, Pluralsight

Puppet 4, Pluralsight

 $\label{thm:condition} \mbox{Amazon Web Services (AWS) Fundamentals for System Administrators \,,} \\ \mbox{Plural sight}$

AWS Certified SysOps Administrator - Associate, acloud guru (without cert) January 2019 — January 2019

Kubernetes Deep Dive, acloud guru (without cert)

February 2019 — February 2019

ITIL (basic + advanced), Pluralsight

November 2019 — November 2019

■ GROUPS

LINUX EDUCATION COMMUNITY HOOK, Poznań

Present

Attending in Linux Education Community Hook

Sysops/Devops meetups, Poznań

System administration meetups every month in Poznań